This lesson can't be learned in the classroom.
The Final is a thriller, horror film directed by Joey Stewart.
A group of high school outcasts get revenge on the students that torment them.
Dane, played by Marc Donato.
Kurtis, played by Jascha Washington.
Bridget, played by Whitney Hoy.
Bradley, played by Justin Arnold.
Emily, played by Lindsay Seidel.
Kelli, played by Laura Ashley Samuels.
The Final is a 2010 American psychological horror thriller film written by Jason Kabolati,
directed by Joey Stewart, and starring Jascha Washington, Julin, Justin S.
Arnold, Lindsay Seidel, Marc Donato, Laura Ashley
Samuels, Ryan Hayden, and Travis Tedford.
It was the last film to feature Washington and Tedford before their retirement.
The film explores themes of mask, high school, kidnapping, revenge, torture.
The tone is dark and intense.